export const quiz = {
    totalQuestions: 12,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: "Who is the main character in Yu-Gi-Oh?",
        answers: ["Pegasus", "Yugi Muto", "Joey Wheeler", "seto-Kaiba"],
        correctAnswer: "Yugi Muto",
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is the name of the card game Yugi and his Friends play?",
        answers: ["YU-GI-OH!!!", "Boss Monsters", "Cards against humanity", "Duel monsters"],

        correctAnswer: 'Duel monsters',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: "What was the name of Seto Kaiba's duel monsters tournament?",
        answers: ["Battle Duelist", "Duel city", "monsters", "Battle city tournament"],
        correctAnswer: "Battle city tournament",
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: "What is the name of Yugi's ace monster?",
        answers: ["Blue eye's white Dragon",
        "Ash Blossom",
        "Man- Eater Bug",
        "Dark Magician"],
        correctAnswer: "Dark Magician",
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: "What was Seto Kaiba's little brothers name ?",
        answers: [
            "Rock Lee",
            "Tears of the kingdom",
            "Mokuba",
            "The nerd who lived"
          ],
        correctAnswer: "Mokuba",
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: "Marik's family was important in the days of the Pharaoh. What was their occupation?",
        answers: [
            "Teachers",
            "pyramid builders",
            "Tomb Keepers",
            "Advertisers"
          ],
        correctAnswer: "Tomb Keepers",
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: "Who was the first duelist Yugi faced against in Duelist Kingdom?",
        answers: [
            "Joey wheeler",
            "Harpies feather duster",
            "Weevil Underwood",
            "All of the above"
          ],
        correctAnswer: "Weevil Underwood",
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: "What was Dark Magicians Attack points",
        answers: [
            "3500", 
            "4600", 
            "2500", 
            "350000"],
        correctAnswer: "2500",
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: "What card is needed to create a Fusion type monster?.",
        answers: [
            "Fusion tunnel",
            "Polymerization",
            "Fusion Gate",
            "All of the above"
          ],
        correctAnswer: "Polymerization",
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: "What Millineum Item does the Pharoh have?",
        answers: ["Millinneum Puzzle", "curly puzzle", "Harpies puzzle", "Millennium Rod"],
        correctAnswer: "Millinneum Puzzle",
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: "What is Tristan's favorite card?",
        answers: [
            "meteonis Drytron",
           "Blue-eyes white dragon", 
           "Cyber commander",
            "Ghost Belle"],
        correctAnswer: "Cyber commander",
      },

      {
        id: 12,
        question: "What duelist never lost a duel in the original yu-gi-oh series",
        answers: [
            "Marik", 
          "Tea Gardner", 
          "yugi Muto",
           "All the above"],
        correctAnswer: "Tea Gardner",
      },


    ],
  };
  